Guide to the Gay men's popular fiction collection, 1931-1992
Gay men's popular fiction collection, 1931-1992
- Stuart, Chad, Blackballed, Greenleaf Classics, PR 350, 1972 (Box 47)
- Stuart, Chad, Mountain Men, Greenleaf Classics, PR 370, 1972 (Box 48)
- Stuart, Chad, Big Guns, Greenleaf Classics, PR 384, 1972 (Box 48)
- Stuart, Chad, E-Mission, Hamilton House, RAM 10-102, 1974 (Box 32)
- Stuart, Chad, The Meat Eaters, Hamilton House, RAM 10-111, 1975 (Box 33)
- Stuart, Chad, Buck, Hamilton House, RAM 10-113, 1975 (Box 33)
- Stuart, Chad, A Presidential Affair, Hamilton House, RAM 10-119, 1975 (Box 33)
- Stuart, Chad, Black Room Terror, Surree House, HIS 69215, 1977 (Box 76)
- Stuart, Chad, Gusher Comin', Surree Ltd, HIS 69203, 1977 (Box 75)
- Stuart, Chad, Animal Man, Surree Ltd, HIS 69227, 1978 (Box 76)
- Sturgeon, Theodore, Venus Plus X, Pyramid Books, F-732, 1960 (Box 53)
- Sturgeon, Theodore, Venus Plus X, Pyramid Books, G-544, 1960 (Box 53)
- Styles, Jordan, Crotch Loving Foursome, Star Dist., Club 123, 1973 (Box 59)
- Styles, Lee, The Gay Whores, Star Dist., SPADE 130, 1973 (Box 65)
- Symon, Jay, The Flaming Suckers, Barclay House, 7082, 1969 (Box 6)
- Talbot, Wes, Bondage Buddies, Greebleaf Classics, AC 188, 1978 (Box 21)
- Talbot, Wes, Stud Show, Greenleaf Classics, AC 156, 1977 (Box 21)
- Talbot, Wes, House Of Studs, Greenleaf Classics, AC 158, 1977 (Box 21)
- Talbot, Wes, Bj Stud, Greenleaf Classics, AC 175, 1978 (Box 21)
- Talbot, Wes, Chicken Master, Greenleaf Classics, AC 209, 1979 (Box 22)
- Talbot, Wes, Blow Boys, Greenleaf Classics, AC 214, 1979 (Box 22)
- Talbot, Wes, Loving Brothers, Greenleaf Classics, AC 216, 1979 (Box 22)
- Talbot, Wes, Golden Shower Surfer, Greenleaf Classics, AC182, 1978 (Box 92)
- Talsman, William, The Gaudy Image, Olympia Press, no. 63, 1958 (Box 38)
- Talsman, William, The Gaudy Image, Olympia Press, TC-302, 1958 (Box 39)
- Talsman, William, The Gaudy Image, Olympia Press, no. 104, 1966 (Box 39)
- Taylor, Don, The Pile Drivers, P. E. C., FL 87, 1970 (Box 52)
- Taylor, Dyson, Bitter Love, Pyramid Books, G-60, 1952 (Box 53)
- Taylor, Dyson, Bitter Love, Pyramid Books, G-278, 1957 (Box 53)
- Taylor, John, Shadows Of Shame, Pyramid Books, G-189, 1956 (Box 53)
- Taylor, Rick, Horny Hijackers, Arena, DS 101, 1982 (Box 1)
- Taylor, Rick, Deep Load, Arena, DS 120, 1983 (Box 1)
- Taylor, Rick, Cruising For A 3-Way, Arena, DS 126, 1983 (Box 2)
- Taylor, Shad, The Master Cowboy, Star Dist., SPADE 103, 1972 (Box 65)
- Tellier, Andre, Twilight Men, Pyramid Books, G-262, 1948 (Box 53)
- Tellier, Andre, Twilight Men, Pyramid Books, X 262, 1948 (Box 53)
- Temple, Butch, Black Hustler, Midwood, 508-60664, 1976 (Box 35)
- Temple, Butch, Divine Head, Surree Ltd, HIS 69196, 1977 (Box 75)
- Temple, Dal, T-Town Tease, GX, Inc., TC 208, n.d. (Box 29)
- Temple, Dal, Pacific Phallusades, GX, Inc., TC 214, n.d. (Box 30)
- Temple, Dal, Phax & Phallusies, GX, Inc., TC 219, n.d. (Box 30)
- Temple, Dal, Hung Overly, GX, Inc., TC 222, n.d. (Box 30)
- Temple, Dal, Land Cruiser, GX, Inc., TC 228, n.d. (Box 30)
- Temple, Dal, Up And Coming, GX, Inc., TC 231, n.d. (Box 30)
- Temple, Dal, Swap Meat, GX, Inc., TC 240, n.d. (Box 31)
- Temple, Dal, Phax & Phallusies, Publisher's Consultants, LR 102, 1977 (Box 50)
- Temple, Dal, Pacific Phallusades, Publisher's Consultants, LR 107, 1977 (Box 50)
- Tempus, Brad, The Gay Brotherhood, Lambda Press, LB 110, 1974 (Box 34)
- Tesch, Gerald, Never The Same Again, Pyramid Books, X 342, 1956 (Box 53)
- Tesch, Gerald, Never the Same Again, Pyramid Books, G342, 1958 (Box 92)
- Thayer, Thurman, The Bugger Brutes, P. E. C., FL 95, 1971 (Box 52)
- Thomas, Aaron, The Beefcake Boys, Corinth Pubns., NB 1858, 1967 (Box 14)
- Thomas, Aaron, A Queen's Fury, Corinth Pubns., NB 1873, 1968 (Box 14)
- Thomas, Aaron, Charlie Darling, Greenleaf Classics, AB 440, 1968 (Box 20)
- Thomas, Aaron, Gay Orgy, Greenleaf Classics, AB 443, 1968 (Box 20)
- Thomas, Aaron, The Family Jewels, Greenleaf Classics, AB 456, 1968 (Box 20)
- Thomas, Aaron, Bitch Boy, Greenleaf Classics, GN 414, 1973 (Box 24)
- Thomas, Aaron, Sixty-Nine Palms, Greenleaf Classics, PR 301, 1971 (Box 46)
- Thomas, Aaron, The Greek Affair, Phenix Publishers, CB 551, 1968 (Box 43)
- Thomas, Aaron, Gay Traders, Phenix Publishers, CB 562, 1968 (Box 43)
- Thomas, Aaron, Good Night, Gentle Boy, Phenix Publishers, LL 764, 1968 (Box 44)
- Thomas, Aaron, Deep Lavender, Phenix Publishers, PR 219, 1969 (Box 44)
- Thomas, Aaron, Queen Of The Road, Phenix Publishers, PR 232, 1969 (Box 44)
- Thomas, Aaron, Senator Swish, Phenix Publishers, CB 553, 1968 (Box 43)
- Thomas, Biff, Gay In San Francisco, Cameo Library, CC-171, 1974 (Box 13)
- Thomas, Eric, Grasp Of Power, Greenleaf Classics, PR 338, 1971 (Box 47)
- Thomas, Len, Hard-Ass Hardhat, Surree Ltd, HIS 69145, 1975 (Box 73)
- Thomas, Len, Suck It, Slave!, Surree Ltd, HIS 69150, 1975 (Box 73)
- Thomas, Len, Forced Entry, Surree Ltd, HIS 69153, 1975 (Box 73)
- Thomas, Len, Hot, Hunky Cruiser, Surree Ltd, HIS 69161, 1976 (Box 74)
- Thomas, Michael, Fun With The Farmboy, Surree Ltd, MH 496, 1979 (Box 83)
- Thomas, Michael, Honey Moon, Surree Ltd, SS 040, 1978 (Box 85)
- Thomas, Orville, The Biker's Kid Brother, Star Dist., SS-1007, 1976 (Box 66)
- Thomas, Stuart, Chicken For Two, Surree Ltd, SS 017, 1976 (Box 84)
- Thompson, Earl, Cum-On Cowhand, Star Dist., WB 128, 1976 (Box 68)
- Thurston, Matthew, Shifting Shadows, Blueboy Library, 80087, 1977 (Box 10)
- Todd, Allen, Hunky Brothers, Arena, MP 102, 1983 (Box 2)
- Todd, Allen, Willing Schoolboys, Surree Ltd, HIS 69430, 1981 (Box 79)
- Todd, Allen H., Shafting Schoolboys, Surree Ltd, HIS 69274, 1978 (Box 78)
- Todd, Allen H., Junior Jocks, Surree Ltd, HIS 69416, 1980 (Box 79)
- Todd, Allen H., Teenage Tease, Surree Ltd, MH 488, 1978 (Box 83)
- Todd, Allen H., Coachin' The Chicken, Surree Ltd, MH 493, 1979 (Box 83)
- Todd, Eric, Swallow My Pride, Surrey House, HIS 06945, 1973 (Box 70)
- Todd, Eric, 3-Way Plug-In, Surrey House, HIS 06975, 1973 (Box 71)
- Todd, Eric, Beachballer, Surrey House, MH 424, 1973 (Box 81)
- Todd, Eric, Beachballer Ii, Surrey House, MH 445, 1974 (Box 82)
- Todd, Eric, Beachballer Iii, Surrey House, MH 457, 1974 (Box 82)
- Toller, Tony, Hard, Hot & Hung, Rough Trade, RT 476, 1979 (Box 56)
- Tomas, Manny, Locker-Room Lust, unknown, -0-, n.d. (Box 89)
- Toomey, K. K., A Bit Of Brown, Surrey House, MH 448, 1974 (Box 82)
- Tower, Peter, Shafted Laddie, Star Dist., WB 102, 1975 (Box 67)
- Towers, Peter, Cock Happy Crew, Star Dist., HS 1004, 1974 (Box 62)
- Towers, Peter, Ride a Hot Marine, Rough Trade, RT-416, n.d. (Box 92)
- Townsend, Larry, Leather Ad Volume 2. S, Greenleaf Classics, GL 149, 1970 (Box 26)
- Townsend, Larry, Leather Ad Volume 1. M, Greenleaf Classics, GL 150, 1970 (Box 26)
- Townsend, Larry, Beware The God Who Smiles, Greenleaf Classics, PR 307, 1971 (Box 46)
- Townsend, Larry, Leather Ad Volume 2 S, Greenleaf Classics, PR 368, 1972 (Box 48)
- Townsend, Larry, The Leatherman's Handbook, LeSalon, -0-, 1972 (Box 34)
- Townsend, Larry, Run, Little Leather Boy, Olympia Press, TC-505, 1971 (Box 39)
- Townsend, Larry, The Scorpius Equation, Olympia Press, TC-513, 1971 (Box 39)
- Townsend, Larry, The Leatherman's Handbook, Olympia Press, TC-3313, 1972 (Box 39)
- Townsend, Larry, 2069 + 1, Phenix Publishers, PR 275, 1970 (Box 46)
- Townsend, Larry, 2069, Phenix Publishers, PR 225, 1969 (Box 44)
- Townsend, Larry, Kiss Of Leather, Phenix Publishers, PR 238, 1969 (Box 45)
- Townsend, Larry, Mickey's One, Phenix Publishers, PR 251, 1970 (Box 45)
- Townsend, Larry, The Fairy King, Phenix Publishers, PR 253, 1970 (Box 45)
- Townsend, Larry, Billy's Club, Phenix Publishers, PR 259, 1970 (Box 45)
- Townsend, Larry, Joven-Cachoteca, Phenix Publishers, PR261, 1970 (Box 92)
- Townsend, Larry, The Long Leather Cord, Greenleaf Classics, PR294, 1971 (Box 92)
- Townsend, Mark, Rape Riot, Tiburon Publishing Co., LLP 127, 1968 (Box 87)
- Townsend, Mark, Slave Revolt, Tiburon Publishing Co., LLP 151, 1969 (Box 87)
- Trainer, Russ, His Brother Love, Satan Press, 108, 1965 (Box 57)
- Trand, Sandy, Fag-A-Rama, Utopia Publications, AH 136, 1974 (Box 88)
- Travis, Ben, The Strange Ones, Softcover, 899X, 1959 (Box 58)
- Travis, Ben, The Strange Ones, Universal, B 226, 1959 (Box 88)
- Tressner Jr., William B., Queens of the Quarter, Regency, 1026, 1970 (Box 92)
- Tressner, William B. Jr, Queens Of The Quarter, P. E. C., FL 48, 1968 (Box 51)
- Trix, Bobby, Pleasure Boy Sucker, Big Boy Series, BB-104, n.d. (Box 12)
- Trocci, H. L., Melody Of Spring, Echelon, IL-242, 1968 (Box 15)
- Trokki, A. L., Quatres Of Cherry Grove, Echelon, IL-233, 1967 (Box 15)
- Tucker, Jerry, Daddy Stud, Greenleaf Classics, AC 195, 1979 (Box 22)
- Tulane, Rick, Over Eighteen Over Eight, GX, Inc., TC 207, n.d. (Box 29)
- Tulane, Rick, His Brother's Keeper, GX, Inc., TC 220, n.d. (Box 30)
- Tulane, Rick, Punk Spunk, GX, Inc., TC 247, 1973 (Box 31)
- Tulane, Rick, Teen Cream, GX, Inc., TC 251, 1973 (Box 31)
- Tulane, Rick, Juvenile Jazz, GX, Inc., TC 255, 1973 (Box 31)
- Tulane, Rick, Stud Starch, GX, Inc., TC 259, 1973 (Box 31)
- Turk, Ruth, More Than Friends, Bantam Books, 0-553-13661-5, 1980 (Box 5)
- Turner, Butch, The Cock Fighters, Rough Trade, RT 483, 1979 (Box 56)
- Turner, Levon, Di's Black Boy, Star Dist., MDB 44, 1984 (Box 63)
- Twigg, J. D., The Gay Governor, Phenix Publishers, PR 287, 1970 (Box 46)
- Tyler, Bryant, Shaft, Arena, GB 127, 1979 (Box 2)
- Tyler, Jason, Chicken Hawk Cop, Greenleaf Classics, AC 169, 1977 (Box 21)
- Tyler, Jason, Bar Buddies, Greenleaf Classics, AC 180, 1978 (Box 21)
- Tyler, Jason, Back-Woods Buddies, Greenleaf Classics, AC 190, 1978 (Box 21)
- Val Baker, Denys, Strange Fulfillment, Pyramid Books, G-341, 1958 (Box 53)
- Van Damm, Dirk, Gay Brothers Bk Ii, Surey Books, HIS 69561, 1987 (Box 80)
- Van Damm, Dirk, Rub a Big Stud, Surey Books, AGR116, 1983 (Box 96)
- van Damn, Dirk, Gay Brothers Book Ii, Star Dist., AGR 165, 1987 (Box 68)
- Van Heller, Marcus, Roman Orgy, Brandon House, 2014, 1966 (Box 12)
- Van Heller, Marcus, The Loins Of Amon, Brandon House, 2031, 1967 (Box 12)
- Van Heller, Marcus, The Wantons, Brandon House, 3006, 1967 (Box 12)
- Van Heller, Marcus, The House Of Borgia, Vol. 1, Greenleaf Classics, GC 216, 1966 (Box 24)
- Van Heller, Marcus, The House Of Borgia, Vol. 2, Greenleaf Classics, GC 217, 1966 (Box 24)
- Van Heller, Marcus, Adam And Eve, Grove Press, V-1007-K, 1971 (Box 19)
- Van Heller, Marcus, The Gang Way, Ophelia Press, OPH-111, 1968 (Box 40)
- Van Heller, Marcus, The Ring, Ophelia Press, OPH-112, 1968 (Box 40)
- Van Heller, Marcus, Jailbirds In The Backseat, Ophelia Press, OPH-106, n.d. (Box 40)
- Van Heller, Marcus, Terror, unknown, 295, n.d. (Box 89)
- Van Marcus, Carl, Her Brothers Two, Tiburon Publishing Co., LLP 192, 1970 (Box 87)
- Vance, Perry, Dirt Bike Orgy, Rough Trade, RT 433, n.d. (Box 55)
- Vanden, Dirk, All Or Nothing, Global Press, FGL 19, 1970 (Box 38)
- Vanden, Dirk, Who Killed Queen Tom?, Greenleaf Classics, GL 106, 1969 (Box 25)
- Vanden, Dirk, The Leather Queens, Greenleaf Classics, GL 109, 1969 (Box 25)
- Vanden, Dirk, Twin Orbs, Greenleaf Classics, GL 126, 1969 (Box 26)
- Vanden, Dirk, Who Killed Queen Tom?, Greenleaf Classics, PR 376, 1972 (Box 48)
- Vanden, Dirk, I Want It All, Oasis, FGL 11, 1969 (Box 38)
- Vanden, Dirk, All Is Well, Olympia Press, -0-, 1971 (Box 38)
- Vanden, Dirk, All Is Well, Olympia Press, TC-512, 1971 (Box 39)
- Vanden, Dirk, Leather, Greenleaf Classics, GL139, 1969 (Box 95)
- Various, Men Behind Bars, Pyramid Books, F-700, 1957 (Box 91)
- Various, 3 Underground Classics, Guild Press Ltd., -0-, 1971 (Box 92)
- Various, Only a Boy and 14 Other Short Erotic Classics, From 1899 to 1966, Greenleaf Classics, GC292, 1968 (Box 95)
- Vassi, Marco, The Saline Solution, Olympia Press, OPS-27, 1971 (Box 95)
- Versage, Robin, Tops, Bottoms And Sidepockets, Foremost Publications, CL 7, 1965 (Box 17)
- Vickery, Jay, Man Into Boy, Greenleaf Classics, AB 436, 1968 (Box 20)
- Vickery, Jay, Gaydreams, Greenleaf Classics, AB 437, 1968 (Box 20)
- Vickery, Jay, Brandon's Boy, Greenleaf Classics, AB 453, 1968 (Box 20)
- Vidal, Gore, Two Sisters, Bantam Books, 553-05984, 1970 (Box 6)
- Vidal, Gore, Three, Signet Books, T 2131, 1946 (Box 57)
- Vincent, J. B., The Assman Cometh, Surrey House, HIS 06978, 1974 (Box 71)
- Virga, Vincent, Gaywick, Avon, 0-380-75820-2-295, 1980 (Box 4)
- Virga, Vincent, A Comfortable Corner, Avon, 0-380-80895-1-350, 1982 (Box 4)
- Vivien, AndrŽ, Boys In Love, Eiffel Classic, EC 612, n.d. (Box 15)
- Vogel, Doug, Incest Father And Sons, Inc, Paramount, PP 109, 1971 (Box 40)
- Voyager, Krystofalus, The Sons Of Priapus, Greenleaf Classics, GL 154, 1970 (Box 26)
- Wade, Carlson, The Muscle Lovers, Echelon, IL-221, 1967 (Box 15)
- Wade, Carlson, Naked In Sodom, Echelon, IL-234, 1967 (Box 15)
- Wade, Carlson, Boys Of Boles Dorm, Echelon, IL-239, 1968 (Box 15)
- Wade, Carlson, Panty Raid, Selbee Publications, No. C-18, n.d. (Box 57)
- Wade, Richard, Black Man's Chicken, Star Dist., WB 125, 1976 (Box 68)
- Wadsworth, Jack, Cowboys Are For Me, Parisian Press, P 244, 1973 (Box 42)
- Wagman, Paul, Hollywood Homo, International Publications, F60, 1963 (Box 33)
- Walker, Gerald, Cruising, Bantam Books, 13660-7, 1970 (Box 92)
- Wallach, Ira, Muscle Beach, Dell, D357, 1959 (Box 15)
- Ward, Michael, Randy Studs, Surey Books, HIS 69477, 1984 (Box 80)
- Ward, Michael, Tower Of Lust, Surey Books, HIS 69478, 1984 (Box 80)
- Ward, Michael, Randy Pants, Surree Ltd, HIS 69432, 1981 (Box 79)
- Ward, Michael, Little Brother, Surrey House, HIS 69188, 1976 (Box 75)
- Ward, Mike, Runaway Chicken, Surree Ltd, HIS 69244, 1978 (Box 77)
- Ward, Mike, Tom's Big Pole, Surree Ltd, HIS 69249, 1978 (Box 77)
- Ward, Mike, Chicken Delights, Surree Ltd, HIS 69257, 1978 (Box 77)
- Ward, Mike, Man-Handler, Surree Ltd, SS 015, 1975 (Box 84)
- Ward, Mike, Hot Young Houseboy, Surree Ltd, SS 022, 1976 (Box 84)
- Ward, Roger, Holler Uncle, Hamilton House, RAM 10-117, 1975 (Box 33)
- Warman, Donald, Some Of My Best Friends, Ophelia Press, OPH-223, 1970 (Box 40)
- Warren, Patricia Nell, The Front Runner, Bantam Books, 553-08712, 1974 (Box 5)
- Warren, Patricia Nell, The Fancy Dancer, Bantam Books, 0-553-10387-3, 1976 (Box 5)
- Warthan, Paul, The Willing Young Guests, Star Dist., Club 130, 1974 (Box 60)
- Warthan, Petrie, Bathhouse Blues, GX, Inc., TC 276, 1973 (Box 32)
- Watson, J., The Sexual Adventures Of Sherlock Holmes, Olympia Press, TC-511, 1971 (Box 39)
- Waverly, Barry, Man Power, Publisher's Consultants, GY 105, 1978 (Box 50)
- Wayne, Mike, Small Town Boy, Star Dist., HS 1012, 1975 (Box 62)
- Wayne, W. W., Snowbound In Sodom, Greenleaf Classics, PR 303, 1971 (Box 46)
- Wayne, W. W., Park Duty, Greenleaf Classics, PR 318, 1971 (Box 47)
- Webster, Bruce, Locker Room Lovers, Star Dist., HS 1015, 1975 (Box 62)
- Weeks, Barry, Price Per Inch, Greenleaf Classics, GL 102, 1969 (Box 25)
- Weeks, Barry, Cock-Of-The-Walk, Greenleaf Classics, GL 116, 1969 (Box 25)
- Wellington, James, Older Men And Young Boys, Valley Circle Pubn., SV 103, 1971 (Box 88)
- Wells, O.R., All-Stud, Greenleaf Classics, GL134, 1969 (Box 93)
- Welsh, Harvey, Spread Studs, Star Dist., WB 126, 1976 (Box 68)
- Wentworth, Stan, Whipping A Hang-Up, GX, Inc., TC 206, n.d. (Box 29)
- Wersba, Barbara, Run Softly, Go Fast, Bantam Books, Q8713, 1970 (Box 92)
- West, Clarence, The Young Hawks, Utopia Publications, AH 125, 1974 (Box 88)
- West, Hunter, The Greek Way, Gay World Special, -0-, n.d. (Box 19)
- West, Hunter, Male Call, Spade Publishing, SP-114, n.d. (Box 58)
- West, Jim, The Father Affair, Star Dist., SPADE 125, 1973 (Box 65)
- West, Ron, Fire Island Romance, Timely Books, -0-, 1971 (Box 87)
- West, Samuel, Blow Boy, Surree Ltd, HIS 69152, 1975 (Box 73)
- West, Samuel, Tricking The Chicken, Surree Ltd, HIS 69168, 1976 (Box 74)
- West, Samuel, Chicken Trick, Surree Ltd, HIS 69172, 1976 (Box 74)
- West, Samuel, Trick Me Easy, Surree Ltd, HIS 69224, 1977 (Box 76)
- West, Samuel, All Day Sucker, Surree Ltd, HIS 69251, 1978 (Box 77)
- West, Samuel, Turned-On Chicken, Surree Ltd, HIS 69262, 1978 (Box 78)
- West, Samuel, Backdoor Boy, Surree Ltd, HIS 69272, 1978 (Box 78)
- West, Samuel, Dads & Lads, Surree Ltd, HIS 69408, 1980 (Box 79)
- West, Samuel, Stud-Sucker, Surree Ltd, MH 491, 1978 (Box 83)
- West, Samuel, Hard-Headed Dick, Surree Ltd, SS 010, 1975 (Box 84)
- West, Samuel, Chicken Comin' Up, Surree Ltd, SSS 103, 1980 (Box 86)
- West, Samuel, Boardwalk Chicken, Surree Ltd, SSS 111, 1981 (Box 86)
- West, Samuel, Fresh Meat, Surey Books, HIS 69434, 1981 (Box 79)
- West, Samuel, Towel Boy, Surey Books, HIS 69442, 1982 (Box 80)
- West, Samuel, The Cummin' Thing, Surrey House, HIS 69104, 1974 (Box 72)
- West, Samuel, Tasty Trick, Surrey House, HIS 69128, 1974 (Box 72)
- West, Samuel, Cream Of Chicken, Surrey House, HIS 69133, 1975 (Box 73)
- West, Samuel, Down, Boy!, Surrey House, HIS 69140, 1975 (Box 73)
- West, Samuel, Lickin' Lad, Surrey House, HIS 69178, 1976 (Box 74)
- West, Samuel, Boy Meat, Surrey House, MH 463, 1974 (Box 82)
- West, Samuel, Deliveries In The Rear, Surrey House, MH 480, 1975 (Box 83)
- West, Samuel, Straight Sucker, Surrey House, SS 002, 1975 (Box 84)
- Western, Jim, Fraternity Boys, Star Dist., WB 106, 1975 (Box 67)
- Westland, Clint, Jerk Off Buddies, Star Dist., WB 111, 1975 (Box 67)
- Weston, Neil J., Naked Launch Book 1, Phenix Publishers, PR 227, 1969 (Box 44)
- Weston, Neil J., Naked Launch Book Ii, Phenix Publishers, PR 228, 1969 (Box 44)
- Weyburn, Scott, Hunky Bike Slave, Arena Publications, PF-139, 1985 (Box 92)
- Wharton, Jim, Naked Cowboy, Surrey House, GW 111, 1971 (Box 18)
- Wheeler, Samuel, Gay Trip, unknown, -0-, n.d. (Box 89)
- White, Darryl, The Studious Studs, GX, Inc., TC 243, 1972 (Box 31)
- White, Darryl, Old Queens Never Die, GX, Inc., TC 254, 1973 (Box 31)
- White, Darryl, Cocky Cousins, GX, Inc., TC 261, 1973 (Box 31)
- White, James, Marla, Private Editions Books, PE 383, 1966 (Box 48)
- White, Lee, The Satin Prince, All Star Books, AS 91, 1966 (Box 1)
- Whitney, Flynn, Rich Man's Sex Toys, Star Dist., Club 108, 1973 (Box 59)
- Whitney, James, The Big Plunge, GX, Inc., SP 101, n.d. (Box 28)
- Whitney, James, The Endless Spiral, GX, Inc., TC 284, 1974 (Box 32)
- Whittington, Chauncey, 69 Boy St., Echelon, IL-237, 1968 (Box 15)
- Whittington, Harry, Die, Lover, Avon, T-450, 1953 (Box 5)
- Wilder, David, Everybody's Andy, Gay Parisian Press, GP, n.d. (Box 19)
- Wilder, David, Father, Sons, & Lovers, Parisian Press, P 205, 1971 (Box 41)
- Wilhelm, Gale, No Nice Girl, Pyramid Books, G-440, 1936 (Box 53)
- Wilhelm, Lambert, Cop Out, Arena, GB 107, 1978 (Box 2)
- Wilhelm, Lambert, The Sweat Game, Arena, GB 109, 1978 (Box 2)
- Wilhelm, Lambert, Meat, Arena, GB 113, 1978 (Box 2)
- Wilhelm, Lambert, Two Brothers, Arena, GB 117, 1978 (Box 2)
- Wilhelm, Lambert, Brothers In The End, Arena, GB 121, 1979 (Box 2)
- Wilhelm, Lambert, Bugger Boy, Greenleaf Classics, AC 118, 1975 (Box 21)
- Wilhelm, Lambert, Oil Rig Boys, Greenleaf Classics, AC 212, 1979 (Box 22)
- Wilhelm, Lambert, Raped Stud, Greenleaf Classics, AC 213, 1979 (Box 22)
- Wilhelm, Lambert, Son Loving Father, Greenleaf Classics, AC 218, 1979 (Box 22)
- Wilhelm, Lambert, Homecoming Buddies, Greenleaf Classics, AC 220, 1980 (Box 22)
- Wilhelm, Lambert, College Buddies, Greenleaf Classics, AC 223, 1980 (Box 22)
- Wilhelm, Lambert, Snowbound Studs, Greenleaf Classics, AC 224, 1980 (Box 22)
- Wilhelm, Lambert, Fun House Buddies, Greenleaf Classics, AC 227, 1980 (Box 22)
- Wilhelm, Lambert, Tied Up Ranch Hands, Greenleaf Classics, AC 228, 1980 (Box 22)
- Wilhelm, Lambert, Call Boy Brothers, Greenleaf Classics, AC 234, 1980 (Box 22)
- Wilhelm, Lambert, Into Leather, Into Bondage, Greenleaf Classics, AC 244, 1981 (Box 22)
- Wilhelm, Lambert, B & D Hustlers, Greenleaf Classics, AC 254, 1981 (Box 23)
- Wilhelm, Lambert, Heavy Cruisers, Greenleaf Classics, AC 263, 1981 (Box 23)
- Wilhelm, Lambert, Country Studs, Greenleaf Classics, AC 265, 1981 (Box 23)
- Wilhelm, Lambert, In Stocks And Bondage, Greenleaf Classics, AC 267, 1982 (Box 23)
- Wilhelm, Lambert, Masters And Slaves, Greenleaf Classics, AC 269, 1982 (Box 23)
- Wilhelm, Lambert, Dog Collar Boys, Parisian Press, P 216, 1972 (Box 41)
- Wilhelm, Lambert, Too Beautiful, Parisian Press, P 230, n.d. (Box 42)
- Wilkinson, Grace, Angie Makes Friends, Tiburon Publishing Co., LLP 163, 1969 (Box 87)
- Willard, Guy, A Sailor's Pillow Tales, FirstHand Books, -0-, 1992 (Box 93)
- Williams, Carl, Teacher's Chicken, Surey Books, SSS 118, 1981 (Box 86)
- Williams, J. X., Born To Be Gay, Corinth Pubns., SR 597, 1966 (Box 14)
- Williams, J.X., The Bronze And The Wine, Corinth Pubns., LB 1172, 1966 (Box 14)
- Williams, J.X., Pretty Man, Corinth Pubns., SR 604, 1966 (Box 14)
- Williams, J. X., Gay Buddies, Corinth Pubns., NB 1857, 1967 (Box 14)
- Williams, J.X., Passion Panamania, Corinth Pubns., LB 1203, 1967 (Box 14)
- Williams, J. X, Gay Treason, Corinth Pubns., NB 1875, 1968 (Box 14)
- Williams, J.X., Good-Bye My Lover, Corinth Pubns., SR 607, 1966 (Box 15)
- Williams, J.X., Ac-Dc Stud, Greenleaf Classics, EL 371, 1967 (Box 23)
- Williams, Randy, Stage Stud, Blueboy Library, 80088, 1977 (Box 10)
- Williams, Tennessee, Cat On A Hot Tin Roof, Signet Books, S 1590, 1955 (Box 57)
- Williams, Tennessee, Suddenly Last Summer, Signet Books, S 1757, 1958 (Box 57)
- Williams, Tennessee, Sweet Bird Of Youth, Signet Books, D 2095, 1959 (Box 58)
- Willingham, Calder, The Gates Of Hell, Dell, 2799, 1951 (Box 15)
- Wilson, Carter, Treasures On Earth, Avon Books, 63305-1, 1980 (Box 92)
- Wilson, George, Slave Flight, Blueboy Library, BB 110, 1978 (Box 11)
- Wilson, George, Whipping Cream, Numbers, 10005, 1978 (Box 37)
- Wilson, George, Ten Time Hole, Rough Trade, RT 415, n.d. (Box 54)
- Wilson, George, Humping Hustler, Rough Trade, RT 423, n.d. (Box 54)
- Wilson, George, Uncle's Whipping Boys, Star Dist., HS 122, n.d. (Box 62)
- Wilson, George, Boot Camp, Star Dist., SS-1012, 1976 (Box 66)
- Wilson, George, Mr. Carter's Fringe Benefits, Star Dist., WB 112, 1975 (Box 67)
- Wilson, George, Whipped And Creamed, Star Dist., WB 115, 1975 (Box 68)
- Wilson, George *, Boys For Pleasure, Star Dist., WB 124, 1976 (Box 68)
- Wilson, George, Meat Market Man, Surrey House, HIS 06994, 1974 (Box 71)
- Wilson, George, Barebutt Rider, Surrey House, HIS 69111, 1974 (Box 72)
- Wilson, George, Chicken Farm, Surrey House, HIS 69115, 1974 (Box 72)
- Wilson, George, Ski Buns, Surrey House, HIS 69117, 1974 (Box 72)
- Wilson, George, Throat Thriller, Surrey House, MH 460, 1974 (Box 82)
- Wilson, George, Lifeguard For Lunch, Surrey House, MH 464, 1974 (Box 82)
- Wilson, Ron, Leather Lover, Phenix Publishers, PR 226, 1969 (Box 44)
- Wilson, Tom, Cock-Hungry Buddies, Star Dist., CC-106, 1977 (Box 59)
- Windsor, Tony, Growing Up Hard, Star Dist., SS-1031, 1979 (Box 67)
- Wing, Johnathan, Chicken For The Hardhats *, Male Color Illustrated, -0-, n.d. (Box 36)
- Winslow, Ned, Bottoms Up, Unique, -0-, 1966 (Box 88)
- Winston, Sam, Good Buddy, Phenix Publishers, PR 247, 1970 (Box 45)
- Wisher, Peter, Size Queen, Eros Publishing, GGS-107, 1974 (Box 16)
- Wohl, Burton, That Certain Summer, Bantam Books, N8264, 1973 (Box 95)
- Wolff, Germann K., The Tortured Sex, Holloway House, HH-113, 1965 (Box 33)
- Wood, Brian, The Deepest Love, Timely Books, -0-, 1971 (Box 87)
- Wood, Ed, Young, Black And Gay, P. E. C., FL 38, 1968 (Box 51)
- Wood, Ed, Gay Black, Regency, 1028, 1970 (Box 54)
- Wood, H. C., Street Punk, Star Dist., SS-1019, 1978 (Box 66)
- Wood, Jack, Navel Maneuvers, GX, Inc., GW 134, n.d. (Box 19)
- Wood, Spike, Jail House Sucker, Star Dist., SS-1023, 1979 (Box 67)
- Woodward, Mike, Superstar Stud, Arena, DS 102, 1982 (Box 1)
- Woodward, Mike, Hard Packer, Arena, DS 105, 1982 (Box 1)
- Woodward, Mike, Brothers All The Way, Arena, DS 124, 1983 (Box 1)